(Raj:)It's true. I've seen him at the beach.
He's like a human chicken wing.
(Howard:)Leonard, come on.
(Leonard:)-Fine, I'll ask if she has a friend for you.
-A hot friend.
(Howard:)-Right.
-And tall.
(Howard:)I want our kids to be able to ride
Space Mountain before they're 20.
(Leonard:)I'll see what I can do.
Hey, guess what I heard today.
(Sheldon:)I'd imagine you heard
any number of things today.
(Sheldon:)When you arrived at work,
you undoubtedly heard:
"Hello. How are you, Raj?"
You're wearing a new sweater vest,
you may have heard:
"New sweater vest?" And possibly,
though less likely, "Nice sweater vest."
(Raj:)Why don't I just tell you
what I heard today?
(Sheldon:)That would probably save us
some time.
(Raj:)Saturday night
at the comic-book store...
(Raj:)...they're having a Mystic Warlords
of Ka-ah tournament. First prize is $500.
(Raj:)-If we team up, we'd be unstoppable.
-I'm sorry, Raj.
(Sheldon:)I have no interest in playing a game
in which I find no challenge.
-But what about the money?
-I have money.
(Raj:)But this is other money.
(Sheldon:)How does it differ
from the money I have?